{
    "id": "d253ab10c72740b4a429a57ee8565f6a",
    "title": "General Grammar Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "It …………………… for the past month.",
            "description": "The present perfect is more common with the time expressions for and since.",
            "answers": [
                "didn't rain",
                "hasn't rained",
                "was not raining"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "Fossil fuels ………………………… coal and petrol are harmful to the environment.",
            "description": "We use such as to give examples.",
            "answers": [
                "such as",
                "like",
                "for example"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "The girl ....................... is sitting in that corner is my neighbor’s daughter.",
            "description": "We use who to refer to people.",
            "answers": [
                "who",
                "which",
                "whom"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "You …………………………. pay for that drink.",
            "description": "When need is a modal auxiliary verb, questions and negatives are made without do.",
            "answers": [
                "don't need",
                "need not",
                "need not to"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "You ......................... get a second opinion.",
            "description": "Had better is used to give strong advice. ",
            "answers": [
                "have better",
                "had better",
                "had better to"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "None of these answers …………………………… correct.",
            "description": "Use a singular verb after none.",
            "answers": [
                "are",
                "is"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "She doesn’t have ………………………. friends.",
            "description": "Not any means the same as no.",
            "answers": [
                "no",
                "any",
                "none"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "…………………………. was there to rescue him.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Nobody",
                "Anybody",
                "Noone"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "That wasn’t ………………………… right.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "quiet",
                "quite"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "…………………………… fire, call",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "In case",
                "If",
                "In case of"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "Things are getting …………………..",
            "description": "Worse is the comparative form of bad.",
            "answers": [
                "bad",
                "worser",
                "worse"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "We lost the deal ………………………….. your obstinacy.",
            "description": "Because of is a preposition. It is followed by a noun. ",
            "answers": [
                "because",
                "because of"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        }
    ]
}